wbai.org 2018-08-29

# WBAI-FM - Local Board Elections

WBAI.org Privacy Policy  

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?** When donating or contacting us via our Web site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, bank information or other details necessary to implement the transaction or communication.

**When do we collect information?** We collect information from you when you make a donation,, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?** We may use the information we collect from you when you register, donate, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or process your transactions.

**How do we protect visitor information?** Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible and we use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit card or banking information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user makes a donation, enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are neither stored nor processed on our servers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?** We along with Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) to analyze aggregate visitor preferences only. 

**Third-party disclosure** We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**Third-party links** We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act** CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:** Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it at the bottom of our Home Page, on our About Page, and on any page that solicits visitor information.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the pages specified above. 

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.

Users are able to change their personal information by emailing or phoning us.

**How does our site handle do not track signals?** We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)** When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices** The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices, we will take the following responsive action: Should a data breach occur we will notify effected users, via email, within 2 days of he discovery of the breach. 

**The CAN-SPAM Act** is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

**We collect your email address in order to:** process and invoice donations, deliver our Newsletter (upon request) and reply to online communication from the user. 

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at** [buddy@wbai.org](mailto:buddy@wbai.org). 

**Contacting Us** If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.wbai.org  
buddy@wbai.org

388 Atlantic Avenue  
Brooklyn, New York 11217  
718-780-8800

Last updated 04/12/2016
